[
    {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "Shortcut key to undo last action",
    "answer": "Ctrl+Z"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "The process of hiding internal details",
    "answer": "Abstraction"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "The process of binding data and methods",
    "answer": "Encapsulation"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "Ability of object to take many forms",
    "answer": "Polymorphism"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "Mechanism of acquiring features from another class",
    "answer": "Inheritance"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "Data structure used in recursion",
    "answer": "Stack"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "Fastest type of memory in a computer",
    "answer": "Cache"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "Device used to convert digital signals to analog",
    "answer": "Modem"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "Full form of URL",
    "answer": "Uniform Resource Locator"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "Protocol used to transfer web pages",
    "answer": "HTTP"
  }
]